Guide to the 3-D image collection, 1840-2012.
3-D image collection
- Series II. Stereoscopes and Cameras
  - Stereoscopes and View Sets
    - Viewers & View Sets 1950s-2012
      - Fifty-Six Scenes of the Grand Canyon of Arizona in Three Dimension Photography with viewer (Box 44)
      - Stereo Realist scope with slides in black box (Box 53)
      - Kodaslide Stereo Viewer II (corded) with bulb and slides in red box (Box 53)
      - Stereo Realist scope with slide labels, brush, holding box, slide cases, and other materials in green box (Box 53)
      - Nucor 3-D Viewer: 24 Animal Action Slides (Box 57)
    - View-Master Sets
      - Star Trek: The Motion Picture Set, 1980 (Box 46)
      - The Royal Wedding Set, 1981 (Box 46)
        Prince Charles and Lady Diana
      - The Dukes of Hazzard Set, 1982 (Box 46)
        Canister
      - Popeye View-Master and stereo views, 1999 (Box 47)
      - Wuzzles Gift Set: 3-D Viewer and 3 Reels, 1985 (Box 47)
      - Voltron Gift Set: 3-D Viewer and 3 Reels, 1984 (Box 47)
      - Wrestling Superstars Gift Set: 3-D Viewer and 3 Reels, 1985 (Box 47)
      - View-Master box of stereoscope viewer and 56 reels (Box 48)
      - Jim Pomeroy - Stereo Views (Box 48)
        Set of viewer and reels
      - Gylden Storm (Box 48)
      - Bugs Bunny View-Master Package (Box 49)
      - Talking View-Master Set (Box 50)
      - Talking View-Master container (Box 68)
      - Space theater in the round projector set, MU-2382
        Featuring Buck Rogers, Flash Gordon, and Star Trek
      - Talking View-Master Spiderman gift pack, MU-2383
      - View-Master 3-D Trvia Quiz Game, 1984 (Box 50)
        Includes second board and Game Book
      - Thriller Gift Set: 3-D Viewer and 3 Reels, 1984 (Box 52)
      - Hammerman Gift Set: 3-D Viewer and 3 Reels, 1991 (Box 52)
      - The Incredibles Gift Set: 3-D Viewer and 3 Reels, 2004 (Box 52)
      - Spongebob Squarepants 3D Viewer and 3 Reels, 2003 (Box 52)
  - Cameras
    - Fine Stereo Cameras
      - 1 Small Camera (Box 63)
      - 1 Large Camera (Box 63)
    - Stereo Cameras & Sets
      - Nimslo/Nishiko Camera Ads, 1984 (Box 65, Folder 1)
      - Linex Flash Gun (Box 65)
      - Nimslo Camera, 35mm 3D (Box 65)
      - Nimslo Camera Case, 35mm 3D (Box 65)
      - Linex Stereo Camera and Viewer (Box 65)
      - Coronet 3D Camera (Box 65)
      - Kodak Stereo Camera (Box 66)
        Kodak Anaston Lens; f/3.5, 35 mm
      - Iloca Hamburg Camera (Box 66)
        Jlitar, 1:3.5/35, 321646B
      - Universal Steré-All Camera (Box 66)
        Tricor Matched; F 3.5, 35 mm
      - Stereo Realist Camera (Box 66)
        f 3.5-22
      - Delta Stereo Camera (Box 66)
      - Stereocrafters, Inc. Videon Camera (Box 66)
        f 3.5-16, 24 mm
      - View-Master Personal Stereo Camera (Box 66)
        f 3.5, 25-mm
      - Haneel Tri-Vision Camera (Box 66)
        f 8, 11, 16
      - Le Glyphoscope (Box 66)
      - Metal Piece (slide?) (Box 66)
        seems to go with camera below
      - Cornu Ontoscope Camera (Box 66)
        Tessar 1:4.5, f 8.5, Carl Zeiss Jena Nr. 689456
      - Verographe (Box 66)
        Transpar 1:6.3, F 54, No. 629
      - Pentax Stereo Adapter 49mm Set (Box 66)
        30348
      - Asahi Pentax Stereo Viewer II (Box 66)
    - Stereo Cameras Cases and Accessories
      - Stereo Realist case (Box 67)
      - Steré-All case (Box 67)
      - Kodak case (Box 67)
      - View-Master Personal Stereo case (Box 67)
      - Stereo Realist Attachment for Photo flash (Box 67)
      - Stereo Realist lenses in case (Box 67)
      - black case with green lining (Box 67)
      - Box with Steré-All Instruction Manual (Box 67)
- Series III. Printed Materials
  - Magazines, Booklets, and Comics
    - Pornographic Advertising and Magazines
      - Adam magazine, Volume 26, Numbers 5-10, 12; Volume 27, Numbers 1-3 (Box 13)
      - Private Mellenium magazine (Box 14)
      - Live! magazine, August 1982, February 1983 (Box 14)
      - Adult Cinema Review magazine, March 1983 (Box 14)
      - Oui magazine, June 1984 (Box 14)
      - Erotic Film Guide magazine, May 1983 (Box 14)
      - Velvet Talks! magazine, January 1982 (Box 14)
      - Video-X magazine, July 1983 (Box 14)
      - Best of Marilyn Chamber's Club magazine, Number 16, 1982 (Box 14)
      - Intimacy magazine, Volume 5, Number 1, 1995 (Box 14)
      - Photo magazine, May 1983 (Box 15)
      - Sports Illustrated magazine, Winter 2000 (Box 15)
      - Hot Shots magazine, Fall 1981 (Box 15)
      - High Society magazine, January 1984 (Box 15)
      - Velvet magazine, January 1985 (Box 15)
      - International magazine, April 1983, January 1984 (Box 15)
      - Club magazine, May 1984 (Box 15)
    - Catalogs & Booklets
      - Catalogue of the Centennial Photographic Company's Views of the International Exhibition (copy), 1876 (Box 18)
      - Modern Stereo Equipment: The Picture Guide to usable cameras, viewers, projectors, and accessories (Box 18)
      - A Trip Around the World booklet (Box 18)
      - Picture it in Stereo: A Kodak publication (Box 18)
      - 3-D Book Productions catalog, 1987-1988 (Box 18)
      - Concession Stand: A Stereo Book by Tom Petrillo (Box 18)
      - Photographing in 3-D by David Burder and Pat Whitehouse (Box 18)
      - Das 3D-Magazin ad (Box 18)
      - Space Shots 3-D ad, May 5-7, 1952 (Box 18)
      - The National Stereoscopic Association 14th Annual Convention booklet, August 19-21, 1988 (Box 18)
      - Stereo Photography in Rochester, New York up to 1900 compiled by Robert Penn Fordyce, 1975 (Box 18)
      - National Stereoscopic Association Membership Directories, 1982-1985 (Box 18)
      - Iterations: The New Image, and 3D Artist booklet (Box 18)
      - CyberBook: The World's Only 3-D Stereoscopic Notebook Computer booklet (Box 18)
      - Eclipse Comics 3-D Ad (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - 3-D Articles (newsprint), 1980-1989 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - 3-D Articles (Xeroxes), 1980-1988 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Advertisements and Articles
      - Kodak 3-D Brochures (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Viewmaster Camera & Viewer Ads -- Nat. Geo., 1947-1953 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Stereo Realist Camera Ads -- Nat. Geo., 1949-1952 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Assorted Stereo Camera Ads -- Nat. Geo., 1953-1956 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Bolex Stereo Camera Ads -- Nat. Geo., 1952-1953 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Kodak Stereo Camera Ads -- Nat. Geo., 1954-1956 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Assorted 3-D Ads & Catalogs (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Christ of Gala Ads (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - Sears Ads, 1908 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Sears Ad, 1927 (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - Sears Ads, 1902 (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - Sears Ads, 1902 (Box 19, Folder 12)
      - Sears Ads, 1902 (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - American Cinematographer, July 1983 (Box 20)
      - Cinefantastique Special Double Issue Vol 13 No 6/Vol 14 No 1 (Box 20)
      - Super 8 Filmaker (3 Issues: Volume Five Number Seven-Eight, Volume Six Number One) (Box 20)
      - Photography, October 1954 (Box 20)
      - Lens' On Campus Magazine, February 1985 (Box 20)
      - Cinefantastique Special Double Issue Vol 12 No 2/Vol 12 No 3 (Box 20)
      - Cinefantastique Volume 13 Number 5 (Box 20)
      - American Cinematographer (2 issues), February 1983, October 1984 (Box 20)
      - American Film, June 1983 (Box 20)
      - Video, June 1982 (Box 20)
      - Video Review, August 1983 (Box 20)
      - Modern Photography, December 1982 (Box 20)
      - Photo graphic, February 1990 (Box 20)
      - Scientific American (2 issues), April 1982, September 1986 (Box 21)
      - Omni, September 1982 (Box 21)
      - Popular Mechanics, March 1983 (Box 21)
      - Science & Mechanics, May/June 1983 (Box 21)
      - Popular Mechanics, October 1956 (Box 21)
      - ScienceWorld, October 6, 1986 (Box 21)
      - Military History, April 1986 (Box 21)
    - Science Fiction, Starlog, and Fangoria
      - Famous Monsters of Filmland #64 (Box 22)
      - Famous Monsters of Filmland #183, May 1982 (Box 22)
      - Famous Monsters #158, 1980 (Box 22)
      - CineMagic Number 35 (Box 22)
      - Film Fantasy Yearbook, March 1983 (Box 22)
      - Fantastic Films Collectors Edition #21, January 1981 (Box 22)
      - Fantastic Films #35, September 1983 (Box 22)
      - Starburst 3D Special Issue No. 64 (Box 22)
      - Discover, May 1988 (Box 22)
      - Starlog Numbers 4-4-5, 54-55, 61, 66, 69-70, 74-75 (Box 23)
      - Fangoria Numbers 9, 18-19, 21-22, 30-31, 37 (Box 23)
      - The Bloody Best of Fangoria (Box 23)
    - Stereo World
      - Stereo World Cumulative Index to Volumes 1-8, 1982 (Box 25)
      - Stereo World (Volumes 2-6), May/June 1975 - January/February 1980 (Box 25)
      - Stereo World (Volumes 7-10, 13-15), March/April 1980 - January/February 1989 (Box 26)
    - Comics
      - 3-D Heroes No. 1 (Box 27)
      - 3-D Bullwinkle and Rocky No. 1, 1986 (Box 27)
      - Hollywood 3-D No. 7 (Box 27)
      - Hamster Vice in 3-D No. 2 (Box 27)
      - 3-D Wimmen's Comics No. 12 (Box 27)
      - G.I. Joe 3-D No. 1-3, 1987 (Box 27)
      - The Flintstones 3-D No. 1-3, 1987 (Box 27)
      - Goldyn in 3-D No. 1 (Box 27)
      - The Weird Tales of Basil Wolverton No. 2 (Box 27)
      - Twisted 3-D Tales No. 1 (Box 27)
      - Spectacular Tor 3D No. 1 & 2, 1986 (Box 27)
      - The Three Stooges 3D No. 2, 1986 (Box 27)
      - Sheena Queen of the Jungle 3-D #1, 1984 (Box 27)
      - The Transformers 3-D No. 1-3, 1987-1988 (Box 27)
      - Will Eisner's 3-D Classics No. 1, featuring Spirit, 1985 (Box 27)
      - Star Wars 3-D No. 1, 1987 (Box 27)
      - Larry Harmon's Laurel & Hardy 3-D No. 2, 1987 (Box 27)
      - The Three Stooges 3-D No. 3, 1987 (Box 27)
      - 3-D Red Mask (Box 27)
      - Gumby 3-D No. 1, 1986 (Box 27)
      - Rat Fink 3-D Number 6, 1986 (Box 27)
      - Hamster Vice in 3-D No. 1, 1986 (Box 27)
      - PictureScope Jungle Adventures No. 3 (Box 27)
      - Krazy Kat No. 5 (Box 27)
      - Bizarre 3-D Zone No. 1, 1985 (Box 28)
      - 3D Lars of Mars No. 1, 1987 (Box 28)
      - Laffin' Gas: Special in 3-D No. 6 (Box 28)
      - Jet 3-D: "The Devil Machine" No. 10 (Box 28)
      - Normalman 3-D Annual No. 1, 1986 (Box 28)
      - Against Blackshard 3-D No. 1, 1986 (Box 28)
      - The New Wave versus The Volunteers No. 2, 1987 (Box 28)
      - Robotech in 3-D No. 1 (Box 28)
      - Ms. Tree's 1950's Three-Dimensional Crime No. 1, July 1987 (Box 28)
      - Adolescent Radioactive Black Belt Hamsters 3-D No. 1, 1996 (Box 28)
      - Adolescent Radioactive Black Belt Hamsters 3-D No. 2-4, 1986 (Box 28)
      - 3D Alien Terror No. 1, 1986 (Box 28)
      - Alien Worlds No. 1 (Box 28)
      - AV in 3D; Normalman, Flaming Carrot, Ms. Tree (Box 28)
      - Betty Boop in 3-D No. 1 (Box 28)
      - The Three Stooges 3D No. 1, 1986 (Box 28)
      - Salimba No. 1-2, 1985 (Box 28)
      - Electric Fear No. 4, 1987 (Box 28)
      - Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde No. 1 (Box 28)
      - DNAgents No. 1, 1985 (Box 28)
      - Dick Tracy in 3-D No. 1, 1986 (Box 28)
      - Three-Dimensional Destroy!! (Box 28)
      - Steve Canyon 3-D (Box 28)
      - Michael Jackson as Captain EO (Box 28)
      - Gumby 3-D No. 2-5, 1986-1987 (Box 28)
      - Captain 3-D No. 1 (Box 29)
      - True 3D No. 1 (Box 29)
      - Felix the Cat 3D No. 1, 1954 (Box 29)
      - Kilroys (Box 29)
      - Adventures into the Unknown! No. 56-57 (Box 29)
      - Adventures in 3-D No. 1 (Box 29)
      - World's First! Featuring Let's Give it a Whack (Box 29)
      - The Original Three Dimension Comics (Box 29)
      - Little Eva (Box 29)
      - 3-D-Ell featuring Rootie Kazootie (Box 29)
      - The Amazing Adventures of Holo-man (Box 29)
      - 3-D Adventure Comics No. 1 (Box 29)
      - Battle for a Three Dimensional World (Box 29)
      - Seduction of the Innocent! No. 1, 1985 (Box 29)
      - Seduction of the Innocent! No. 2 (Box 29)
      - CyberRad No. 1, 1991 (Box 29)
      - Boffo Laffs No. 1, 1986 (Box 29)
      - Larry Harmon's Bozo in 3-D No. 1, 1987 (Box 29)
      - BraveStarr in 3-D No. 1, 1987 (Box 29)
      - Richie Rich and Casper the Friendly Ghost in 3-D No. 1, 1987 (Box 29)
      - The New Wave versus The Volunteers No. 1 (Box 29)
      - Ms. Tree 3-D (Box 29)
      - Mr. Monster's 3D Hi-Octane Horror No. 1 (Box 29)
      - Miracleman 3D No. 1 (Box 29)
      - Merlin Realm in 3D No. 1 (Box 29)
      - Laurel & Hardy in 3-D No. 1, 1986 (Box 29)
      - Little Nemo in Slumberland in 3-D No. 1 (Box 29)
      - 3-D Laser Fraser and Pressbutton No. 1 (Box 29)
  - Movie and Television Related
    - Promotional material
      - Gorilla at Large & Inferno Promos -- Providence, RI, May 10, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Gorilla at Large Promos -- Rochester, NY, July 19, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Cinema Magazine (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Friday the 13th -- 3D Publicity Photos (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - 3D Movie Brochures (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Friday the 13th -- 3D Small Lobby Cards (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Parasite -- Lobby Fold-Out, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Parasite -- Lobby Fold-Out, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Parasite -- Lobby Fold-Out, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Parasite -- Lobby Fold-Out, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - Parasite -- Lobby Fold-Out, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - Spacehunter: Adventure in the Forbidden Zone in 3-D Fold-Out, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - Metalstorm: The Destruction of Jared-Syn in 3-D, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - Gorilla at Large, Undated (Box 64, Folder 1)
        Campaign book
      - Gorilla at Large, 1982 (Box 64, Folder 1)
        Poster for a viewing in Rochester
      - Phantom of the Rue Morgue, 1954 (Box 64, Folder 3)
      - Fox-o-Rama, 1994 (Box 64, Folder 5)
        Two days of 3-D television
    - Posters
      - Hondo glasses, button (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Hondo posters (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - Parasite poster, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Comin' at Ya poster, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Dynasty, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Amityville 3-D poster, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - The Man who Wasn't There poster, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - Treasure of the Four Crows, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Chain Gang in 3D (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - Hit the Road Running poster (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - Rottweiler poster (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Jaws 3-D poster, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Jaws 3-D poster, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - Jaws 3-D poster (preview), 1982 (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - Space Heater poster, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 15)
      - Space Heater poster II, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 16)
      - Metalstorm poster, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 17)
      - Metalstorm (extra), 1983 (Box 31, Folder 18)
      - Friday the 13th Part 3, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 19)
      - Friday the 13th (3-D poster) 2 copies, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 20)
      - Friday the 13th (3-D poster) (Bad), 1982 (Box 31, Folder 21)
      - Moonlighter Poster (Beat) (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - Flight to Tangiers (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - The Maze (Poster) (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - Man in the Dark (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - House of Wax, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - House of Wax (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - Dial M for Murder, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - Creature from the Black Lagoon, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - It Came from Outer Space, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - Creature from the Black Lagoon, It Came from Outer Space Combo Sheet, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Andy Warhol's Frankenstein, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - Andy Warhol's Frankenstein, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 12)
      - Frankenstein's Bloody Terror, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 13)
      - Love in 3D (Box 32, Folder 14)
      - The Stewardesses (Box 32, Folder 15)
      - International Stewardesses (Box 32, Folder 16)
      - The Stewardesses from 3D to 3X (Box 32, Folder 17)
      - Supersonic Super Girls (Box 32, Folder 18)
      - Manage a Trois, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 19)
      - Friday the 13th, Part 3 (3D) Cardboard Display, 1982 (Mapcase-folder 1)
      - Star Trek: The Motion Picture (cardboard display), 1979 (Mapcase-folder 2)
    - Lobby Cards
      - Parasite -- Lobby Fold-Out (open), 1982 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - Parasite (Comp.), 1982 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Comin' at Ya (Comp.), 1981 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - The Man who Wasn't There Lobby Cards (Comp.), 1983 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - Space Hunter (Comp.), 1983 (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - Treasure of the Four Crowns (Comp.), 1982 (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - Friday the 13th (Comp.), 1982 (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - I, The Jury (1 card), 1953 (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - Sangaree (6 cards), 1953 (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - Second Chance (1 card), 1953 (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - Miss Sadie Thompson (1 card), 1953 (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - Those Redheads from Seattle (2 cards), 1953 (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - The Nebraskan (2 cards), 1953 (Box 33, Folder 13)
      - The Maze (Comp.) (Box 33, Folder 14)
      - Gun Fury (4 cards), 1953 (Box 33, Folder 15)
      - The Stranger Wore a Gun (4 cards), 1953 (Box 33, Folder 16)
      - Inferno (2 cards), 1953 (Box 33, Folder 17)
      - Man in the Dark (6 cards), 1953 (Box 33, Folder 18)
      - The Glass Web (1 card), 1953 (Box 33, Folder 19)
      - Wings of the Hawk (Comp.), 1953 (Box 33, Folder 20)
      - Jaws 3-D Ads, July-September 1983 (Box 33, Folder 21)
      - Metalstorm Ads, August 1983 (Box 33, Folder 22)
      - Man Who Wasn't There Ads, August 1983 (Box 33, Folder 23)
      - Space Hunter Ads, May 1983 (Box 33, Folder 24)
      - Amityville 3-D Ads, November-December 1983 (Box 33, Folder 25)
      - Treasure of the Four Crowns Ads, April-May 1983 (Box 33, Folder 26)
      - Andy Warhol's Frankenstein Ads, May 1983 (Box 33, Folder 27)
      - Movies --Small Releases -- Ads, May-July 1983 (Box 33, Folder 28)
      - 3-D Articles, 1983-1988 (Box 33, Folder 29)
      - The Mad Magician, 1954 (Box 64, Folder 2)
      - I, The Jury, 1953 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Album Covers
    - Nile Rodgers: B-Movie, 1985; SR-6482 (Box 34)
    - The Cramps: Off the Bone, 1983; SR-6483 (Box 34)
    - Grand Funk: Shinin' On, 1974; SR-6484-6485 (Box 34)
      One with 3D glasses intact in cover, one without
    - Toronto: Girls Night Out, 1983; SR-6486-6487 (Box 34)
      Two records with different images
    - UB40, SR-6488 (Box 34)
    - "The British are Coming": Interviews with the Beatles, 1982; SR-6489 (Box 34)
    - Paul McCartney: Suitable for Framing, SR-6490 (Box 34)
    - Scouse the Mouse' (Richard Starkey), 1983; SR-6491 (Box 34)
    - "Weird Al" Yankovic in 3-D, 1984; SR-6492 (Box 34)
    - Johnny Cash: The Holy Land, SR-6493 (Box 34)
    - The Rolling Stones: Their Satanic Majesties Request, SR-6494 (Box 34)
    - Captain Beyond, 1970; SR-6495 (Box 34)
  - Cereal Boxes
    - Sugar Bear 3-D viewer -- Sharks (Box 35, Folder 1-2)
    - Sugar Bear 3-D viewer -- Tigers (Box 35, Folder 3-4)
    - Sugar Bear 3-D viewer -- Alligator (Box 35, Folder 5-6)
    - Kellogg's 3-D Paint Set (Box 35, Folder 7-8)
    - "Fireball Action" Honey Comb Poster (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - "PMX Fever" Honey Comb Poster (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Super Golden Crisp (2 boxes), February 25, 1988 (Box 35)
    - Dinersaurs (3 boxes), 1988 (Box 35)
    - Super Golden Crisp (2 boxes), July 22, 1986 (Box 35)
    - Kellogg's Sugar Corn Pops (2 boxes), December 11, 1982 (Box 35)
    - Kellogg's Frosted Rice Krispies (2 boxes), July 8, 1983 (Box 35)
    - Kellogg's Froot Loops (2 boxes), September 20, 1983 (Box 35)
    - Kellogg's Sugar Corn Pops (2 boxes), May 31, 1984 (Box 35)
    - Post Honey-Comb (2 boxes), September 6, 1986 (Box 35)
    - Super Golden Crisp (2 boxes), April 27, 1988 (Box 35)
    - Kellogg's Frosted Flakes (2 boxes), November 1, 1990 (Box 35)
    - Cap'n Crunch (1 box) (Box 35)
    - Trix (1 box), April 21, 2004 (Box 35)
    - Ghost Busters (6 boxes, 2 of each image) (Box 35)
    - Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles (2 boxes) (Box 35)
    - Freakies (2 boxes) (Box 35)
- Series IV. Lenticular, Holographic, and Anaglyph Processes
  - Lenticular
    - Postcards
      - Animals
        - Bears (Box 30, Folder 1-2)
        - Deer (Box 30, Folder 3-6)
        - Deer on Cliff (Box 30, Folder 7-8)
        - Fawn in Woods (Box 30, Folder 9-10)
        - Chipmunks (Box 30, Folder 11-12)
        - Owl (Box 30, Folder 13-14)
        - Hawk (Box 30, Folder 15-16)
        - Flying Ducks (Box 30, Folder 17-18)
        - Gorilla (Box 30, Folder 19-20)
        - Parakeets (Box 30, Folder 21-22)
        - Fish (Box 30, Folder 23-28)
        - Seahorses (Box 30, Folder 29-30)
        - Horses (Box 30, Folder 31-34)
        - Running Horses (Box 30, Folder 35-38)
        - Dogs (Box 30, Folder 39-40)
        - Schnauzer (Box 30, Folder 41-12)
        - Kitten (Box 30, Folder 43-44)
        - Puppy (Box 30, Folder 45-46)
        - Chicks (Box 30, Folder 47-48)
      - Children's Motifs
        - Kids Praying (Box 30, Folder 49-50)
        - Dolls (Box 30, Folder 51-52)
        - Knitting Doll (Box 30, Folder 53-54)
        - Cinderella (Box 30, Folder 55-56)
        - Mickey Mouse (Box 30, Folder 57-58)
        - Bambi (Box 30, Folder 59-60)
        - Snow White (Box 30, Folder 61-62)
        - Goldilocks & 3 Bears (Box 30, Folder 63)
        - Jungle Book (Box 30, Folder 64)
        - Kings Island (Box 30, Folder 65-77)
      - Buildings and Tourist Sites
        - New York Buildings (Box 30, Folder 78)
        - Manhattan Skyline (Box 30, Folder 79)
        - Empire State Building (Box 30, Folder 80)
        - New York Buildings (Box 30, Folder 81-82)
        - We Shook up the City (Box 30, Folder 83-84)
        - Statue of Liberty (Box 30, Folder 85-88)
        - United Nations (Box 30, Folder 89-90)
        - Brooklyn Bridge (Box 30, Folder 91-92)
        - Niagara Falls (Box 30, Folder 93-94)
        - White House (Box 30, Folder 95-96)
        - Jefferson Memorial (Box 30, Folder 97)
      - Outdoor Scenes
        - Lake Scene (Box 30, Folder 98-99)
        - Kids by Stream (Box 30, Folder 100-101)
        - Country Scene (Box 30, Folder 102-103)
        - Covered Bridge -- Summer (Box 30, Folder 104-105)
        - Covered Bridge -- Winter (Box 30, Folder 106-107)
        - Hunters (Box 30, Folder 108-109)
        - Fisherman (Box 30, Folder 110-111)
        - Skiers (Box 30, Folder 112-113)
        - Balloons (Box 30, Folder 114-115)
      - People and Portraits
        - Indian Chief (Box 30, Folder 116-117)
        - Winking Girl (Box 30, Folder 118-119)
        - Sun Bunny (Box 30, Folder 120-121)
        - Nature Beauty (Box 30, Folder 122-123)
        - Richard Nixon (Box 30, Folder 124-125)
        - Pope John Paul II (Box 30, Folder 126)
      - Religions
        - Christ (Box 30, Folder 127-128)
        - Madonna and Child (Box 30, Folder 129-130)
        - Christ at Door (Box 30, Folder 131-132)
        - Christ Praying (Box 30, Folder 133-134)
        - The Last Supper (Box 30, Folder 135)
        - Crucifixion (Box 30, Folder 136-137)
        - Cross (Box 30, Folder 138-139)
        - Sacred Heart Christ (Box 30, Folder 140-4141)
        - Our Lady of the Miraculous Medal (Box 30, Folder 142-143)
        - Guardian Angel (Box 30, Folder 144-145)
        - Lord Help Me (Box 30, Folder 146-147)
        - Pieta (Box 30, Folder 148)
        - Praying Hands (Box 30, Folder 149-150)
        - Lord Bless this Home (Box 30, Folder 151-152)
        - Christ Over the City (Box 30, Folder 153-154)
        - Blinking Christ (Box 30, Folder 155-156)
        - Christ in Waterfall (Box 30, Folder 157-158)
        - Christ in Flowers (Box 30, Folder 159-160)
        - Christ Praying (Box 30, Folder 161-162)
        - Christ at Door (Box 30, Folder 163-164)
        - Shroud of Turin (Box 30, Folder 165)
        - Indian Religion (Box 30, Folder 166-173)
      - Space
        - Lunar Module (Box 30, Folder 174-175)
        - Apollo Spaceships (Box 30, Folder 176-177)